So here I've not literally thought of it as much because I was heavily focused on the high quality sound,
as you've noticed, I've even made breakthroughs over there that are not literally in the WW industry.
That's how serious I am. I'm going for that. No wealthy. I'm going for innovation.
Yeah. So, no, not really, I've not, but I'm thinking of it being like an interface when you save.
You can literally at first save, it's going to be regular, save the project's project name,
it is it's it. Then when you try to save it for the next time, like, save that project again,
then the magic happens, then it goes like, do you want to override the project or create an
branch, you know, that is what I want. Then when you create a branch, you end time to that branch.
And when you try to go into the save section, you get that map of other branches and their names.
That's what I'm idealistically thinking, but things can change and you can suggest any better ideas if any.