Okay, so the vision for the DAW is I'm thinking of making it feel very, like, futuristic,
thinking of making it very easy for producers. Like every haddle I've had as a producer,
I want it gone. Like I'm thinking of things like geets like saves for things like
final v1, final v2, final final v3, you know, like I'm thinking of making serious improvements
on the industry and not just be another gimmick DAW, like I want it to be by producers for producers,
you know, like make everything that I felt needed a fix, fixable, like begin a friendly, you know,
very touch and go, like you see something, you try to drag it, it does something and you get feedback
instantly. Not try to be a cockpit at go, at runtime, you know, and very, very high quality sound
for low end users, you know, low end users tend to not get the quality of sound, they deserve,
like, you know, people need high quality sound and I want them to have that. But I,
this is the vision I'm seeing at December 26 for the better for the V1.